Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Page Aircraft Maintenance, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 2003, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  11/26/67. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Page Aircraft Maintenance, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 2003, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  4/30/68. Issue: tools - theft - management's obligation to replace
- Page Aircraft Maintenance, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 2003, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  12/22/69. Issue: rates of pay - method of payment
- Park Sherman Co. vs. USA, Local 2039, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  11/10/58. Issue: discipline - refusal of overtime
- Park Sherman Co. vs. USA, Local 2039, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  2/5/61. Issue: vacation pay
- Parkside Manor vs. Building Service Employees, Local 50, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  8/7/68. Settled
- Parkview Markets, Inc. vs. Warehouse, Production and Maintenance Employees, Local 661, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  2/21/72. Issue: transfers - seniority.
- Patriot-News Co. vs. Harrisburg Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union No. 123, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  6/4/61. Issue: arbitration procedure - appeal to arbitration
- Peerless Supply Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  5/5/65. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Peter Hauptmann Tobacco Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Penn-Dixie Industries, Inc. vs. CLGW, Local 258, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  6/24/74. Issue: rates of pay - holiday pay
- Peoria Institute for Dry Cleaners vs. Int'l. Association of Cleaning and Dye House Workers, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  3/18/55. Issue: rates of pay - wage re-opening clause
- Peoria Institute for Dry Cleaners vs. Int'l. Association of Cleaning and Dye House Workers, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  12/21/55. Issue: contracts - contract modification
- Peoria Institute for Dry Cleaners vs. Int'l. Association of Cleaning and Dye House Workers, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  2/17/55. No decision
- Pepsi-Cola General Bottlers, Inc. vs. Brewery and Soft Drink Workers, Local 20, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  9/23/73. Issue: assignment of jobs - rates of pay
- Perfection Biscuit Co. vs. RWDSU, Local 835, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  9/4/65. Issue: schedules of work - holidays
- Perfection Biscuit Co. vs. RWDSU, Local 835, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  9/2/65. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Pet Milk Co. vs. IBT, Local 916, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  12/28/56. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Petro-Tex Chemical Corp. vs. OCAW, Local 4-227, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  10/10/67. No decision
- Pevely Dairy Co. vs. IUOE, Locals 2, 2A, 2B, and 2C, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  9/17/57. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Pfizer, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Traders, Local 1850, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  1/21/75. No decision.
- Phelps Dodge Aluminum Products Corp. vs. IBEW, Local 702, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  12/12/70. Issue; discipline - discharge.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Miscellaneous Drivers and Helpers, Local 610, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  9/22/62. Issue: overtime - seniority
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, Local 242, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  1/12/63. Issue: assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. vs. Miscellaneous Drivers and Helpers, Local 610, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  4/11/63. Issue: holidays and holiday pay.
- Porter, H. K., Co., Connors Steel Division vs. USA, Local 2250, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  5/8/65. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Porter, H. K., Co., Connors Steel Division vs. USA, Local 2250, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  3/2/67. Issue: rates of pay - classification of jobs
- Porter, H. K., Co., Connors Steel Division vs. USA, Local 2250, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  5/8/65. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Porter, H. K., Co., Laclede-Christy Co. vs. UBCW, District 2, Local 967, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  11/3/54. Issue: layoff - seniority.
- Porter, H. K., Co. vs. UBCW, Local 803, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  5/6/58. Issue: schedules of work - split workweek
- Porter, H. K., Co. vs. UBCW, Local 648, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  3/6/58. Issue: recall - seniority - reinstatement
- Porter, H. K., Co. vs. UBCW, Local 803, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  12/29/59. Issue: layoff - recall
- Pressed Steel Tank Co. vs. USA, District 32, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  9/18/63. No decision
- Proctor and Gamble Manufacturing Co. of Chicago vs. Independent Oil and Chemical Workers, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  7/21/71. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Public Service Co. of Indiana, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1393, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  6/25/63. Issue: assignment of jobs - weather conditions
- Pulitzer Publishing Co., St. Louis Post-Dispatch vs. IUOE, Local 2, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  7/58. No decision.
- Purex Corp., Ltd. vs. ICW, Local 611, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  9/12/56. Issue: arbitrability - timeliness; discipline - discharge
- Purex Corp., Ltd. vs. ICW, Local 611, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 12-13)
  4/12/50. Issue; discipline - discharge.
- Purex Corp. vs. Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Industries Employees' Union, Local 618, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  5/19/73. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Co., American Thermometer Division vs. USA, Local 1979, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  12/27/49. Issue: vacations - layoff.
- Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Co., Fulton-Sylphon Division vs. USA, Local 5431, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  1/24/61. Issue: discipline - overtime
- Robertson, H. H., Architectural Products Division vs. Sheet Metal Workers Int'l. Association (SMW), Local 503, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  11/23/68. Issue: assignment of jobs - ability vs. seniority
- Robins, G. S., and Co. vs. ICW, Local 16, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  4/12/52. Issue: rates of pay - wage re-opening clause
- Robins, G. S., and Co. vs. ICW, Local 16, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  10/14/52. Issue: discipline - discharge; reinstatement - back pay
- Robins, G. S., and Co. vs. ICW, Local 16, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  10/20/52. No decision
- Royal Typewriter Co. Inc. vs. AIW, Local 469, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  10/14/68. Settled
- Rubberoid Co. of St. Louis vs. CLGW, Local 107., 1960 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  6/30/60. Issue: vacation pay
- Rubberoid Co. of St. Louis vs. CLGW, Local 107., 1958 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  12/1/58. No decision
- Ryerson, Joseph T., and Son, Inc. vs. Int'l. Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (BSOIW), Local 518, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  6/23/64. Issue: discipline - working conditions - wash-up time
- Sachs Electric Co. vs. IBT, Local 682, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Safeway Stores, Inc. vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union, Local 363, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  9/16/65. Issue: discipline - discharge
- St. Clair Shoe Manufacturing Co. vs. USW, Local 232, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  8/3/54. Issue: contract interpretation - rates of pay
- St. Joseph Lead Co., Herculaneum, Missouri vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand Workers of America, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  3/6/50. Issue: schedules of work - notice
- St. Joseph Lead Co., Herculaneum, Missouri vs. Federation of Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand Workers of America, Local 132, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  1/26/51. Issue: discipline - layoff.
- St. Joseph Lead Co., Herculaneum, Missouri vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers Union, Local 688, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  6/30/67. Issue: rates of pay
- St. Joseph Lead Co., Bonne Terre, Missouri vs. USA, Local 6242, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  3/3/68. Issue: rates of pay.
- St. Joseph Lead Co., Bonne Terre, Missouri vs. USA, Local 6242, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  8/11/68. Issue: discipline - warnings
- St. Joseph Lead Co., Bonne Terre, Missouri vs. USA, Local 6242, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  8/9, 11, 12/68. Issue: rates of pay - claim for pay of higher classification; discipline warnings; classification of jobs - discontinuance of classification and/or job
- St. Joe Minerals Corp. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  11/29/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- St. Louis Board of Education vs. St. Louis Teachers' Union, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  5/27/74. Issue: probationary employees - termination of employment
- St. Louis Board of Education vs. St. Louis Teachers' Union, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  9/2/74. Issue: assignment of jobs - failure to assign
- St. Louis Car Co. vs. USA, Local 1055, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  5/29/50. Issue: discipline - discharge
- St. Louis Car Co. vs. USA, Local 1055, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  1/26/53. No decision
- St. Louis County Water Co. vs. Utility Workers' Union of America, Local 335, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  2/8/50. Issue: rates of pay.
- St. Louis County Bridge and Grading Co. vs. IBT, Local 682, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  10/31/58. Issue: discharge - negligence and carelessness
- St. Louis Globe-Democrat Publishing Co. vs. St. Louis Newspaper Guild, CIO, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  8/21/47. Issue: shift differentials.
- St. Louis Post Dispatch vs. IUOE, Local 2, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  7/11/58. Issue: interest arbitration - union security, etc.
- St. Louis, City of, Board of Education vs. St. Louis Teachers' Association, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  4/2/74. No award.
- St. Louis County Water Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America (UWU), Local 335, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 5-6)
  7/5/49. Issue: change of schedule - overtime
- St. Louis County Water Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America (UWU), Local 335, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  12/17/49. Issue: wage rates. (No award.)
- St. Louis County Water Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America (UWU), Local 335, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  2/13/57. Issue: layoff - seniority
- St. Louis County Water Co. vs. UWU, Local 448, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  4/22/63. Issue: arbitrability - bidding
- St. Louis Newspaper Publishers' Association vs. St. Louis Typographical Union No. 8., 1958 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  11/10/58. Issue: arbitrability
- St. Louis Restaurant Owners' Association vs. St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of HREU., 1954 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  2/9/54. Issue: part-time employees - fringe benefits - health and welfare programs
- St. Louis Restaurant Owners' Association vs. St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of HREU., 1955 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  3/8/55. Issue: wage re-opener
- St. Louis Restaurant Owners' Association vs. St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of HREU., 1955 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  12/7, 8, 10, 28/55. Issue: interest arbitration. (No award, includes transcript.)
- St. Louis Restaurant Association vs. St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of HREU, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  8/25, 29/55. Issue: wage re-opener
- St. Louis Restaurant Association vs. St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of HREU, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  8/22/55. Issue: compliance with award - duty to furnish information regarding
- St. Louis Restaurant Association vs. St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of HREU, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  8/24/55. Issue: compliance with award - rates of pay - retroactive
- St. Louis Restaurant Association vs. St. Louis Local Joint Executive Board of HREU, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  8/23/55. Issue: wage re-opener
- St. Louis Soft Drink Bottlers, Employers Group, Vess Bottling Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  7/15/62. Issue: reinstatement after sick leave - change in duties, rate of pay
- St. Louis Soft Drink Bottlers, Employers Group, Vess Bottling Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  7/17/62. Issue: change of duties - rate of pay - computation
- St. Louis Soft Drink Bottlers, Employers' Group of St. Louis, Coca-Cola Bottling Corp. of St. Louis vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers Union, Local 688, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  6/27/62. Issue: added duties - creation of a new job
- St. Louis Soft Drink Bottlers, Employers' Group of St. Louis, Coca-Cola Bottling Corp. of St. Louis vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers Union, Local 688, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  12/26/63. Issue: overtime - computation.
- St. Louis Stag Sales, Inc. vs. Brewery Drivers and Helpers, Local 113, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  4/25/66. Issue: discharge - loafing.
- St. Louis Steel Casting, Inc. vs. USA, Local 3671, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  12/21/62. Issue: discharge - insubordination, sub-standard performance
- St. Louis Steel Casting, Inc. vs. USA, Local 3671, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  12/28/62. Issue: elimination of jobs
- St. Louis Steel Casting, Inc. vs. USA, Local 3671, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  10/64. Issue: absences. (Exhibits - no award).
- Sangamo Electric Co. vs. IAM, District 111, Lodge 1986, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  8/12/60. Issue: rates of pay - rate revision - computation change
- Sangamo Electric Co. vs. Selco Union, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  2/12/63. Issue: discharge - unsatisfactory work
- Scheff Manufacturing Co. vs. SMW, Local 93, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  1/8/63. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Schlitz, Jos., Brewing Co. vs. IBT, Local 745, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  3/24/71. Issue: contracting out - bargaining unit work
- Schlueter Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 2393, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  10/10/47. Issue: retirement - termination of employment
- Schlueter Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 2393, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  7/28/48. Issue: rates of pay - computation
- Schlueter Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 2393, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  4/30/48. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Schlueter Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 2393, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  9/10/63. Issue: demotions - right to return to old classification
- Schlueter Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 2393, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  11/20/65. Issue: discipline - negligence and carelessness
- Schlueter Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 2393, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  1/26/66. Issue: bidding - right to bid
- Schnur, E. J., Funeral Home vs. Miscellaneous Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 610, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  7/16/63. Issue: termination of employment - elimination of jobs
- Schultz Folding Box Co. vs. Papercraft Workers' Union No. 409, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  5/20/48. Issue: assignment of jobs - assignment to work outside classification
- Scott County Milling Co. vs. AFGM, Local 108, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  4/1/62. Issue: layoffs
- Scruggs-Vandervoort-Barney, Inc. vs. Department Store, Furniture and Appliance Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local 709, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  5/5/61. Issue: lunch periods - overtime
- Sears, Roebuck and Co. vs. IBT, Local 618, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  2/16/73. No decision
- Semi Steel Casting Co. vs. USA, Local 4323, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  4/24/64. Issue: rates of pay - reduction.
- Service Blue Print and Photo Copy Co. vs. Miscellaneous Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 610, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  5/31/73. Issue: termination of employment - following illness or physical disability.
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  3/15/49. Issue: union security - maintenance of membership
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  3/12/49. Issue: seniority; leaves of absence. (Withdrawn.)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  3/12/49. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority.
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  3/12/49. Issue: seniority; leaves of absence.
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  3/12/49. Withdrawn
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  3/12/49. Issue: bidding - right to bid
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  3/12/49. Issue: rates of pay - lunch periods.
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 23)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  3/12/49. Issue: assignment of jobs - failure to assign
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 25)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 26)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  3/12/49. Issue: assignment of jobs - temporary assignment
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 28)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 29)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  3/12/49. Issue: rates of pay
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  3/12/49. Issue: fringe benefits - bonuses.
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  3/12/49. Issue: rates of pay - change of operation
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 33)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  3/12/49. Issue: shift scheduling and starting time change
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  3/12/49. Issue: discharge. (Withdrawn.)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  3/12/49. Issue: contract interpretation - shift preference
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW (Box 78, Folder 4)
  No date. No award - walkout. (See ff 5.)
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  10/31/51. Issue: walkout -discipline - union representative
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  10/27/51. Issue: leaving the plant without permission - discipline - union representative
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  2/26/54. rates of pay - incentive pay
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  11/14/63. Issue: discharge - theft
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  9/4/64. Issue: bumping into specific job - disability
- Servus Rubber Co. vs. URW, Local 215, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  6/16/67. Issue: discharge - unauthorized absences
- Seymour Wallas and Co. vs. ILGWU, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  3/15/57. Issue: health fund - financial irresponsibility
- Champagne Industries, Inc. vs. USW, Local 2082, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  1/11/67. Issue: assignment of jobs - inventory taking - seniority. (No award.)
- Champagne Co. vs. USW, Local 2082, 1955 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  12/12/55. Issue; discharge - probationary employee
- Champagne Co. vs. USW, Local 2082, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  1/26/56. Issue: reporting pay
- Champagne Co. vs. USW, Local 2082, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  6/17/57. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Champagne Co. vs. USW, Local 2082, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  12/21/62. Issue; recall - temporary work; seniority
- Champagne Co. vs. USW, Local 2082, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  5/14/67. Issue: inventory taking - seniority.
- Shapleigh Hardware Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  5/21/59. Issue: assignment of work outside unit - remedy for improper assignment
- Shapleigh Hardware Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  5/23/59. Issue: assignment of work outside unit - remedy for improper assignment
- Sheffield Steel Corp. vs. USA, Local 13, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  3/25/48. Issue: rates of pay - wage increases - retroactive pay. (No award.)
- Sheffield Steel Corp. vs. USA, Local 13, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 18-19)
  4/30/48. Issue: rates of pay - wage increases - retroactive pay. (See ff 17.)
- Shell Oil Co. vs. OCAW, Local 7-210., 1974 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  5/1/74. Issue; discharge -substandard performance
- Shell Oil Co. vs. PPF, Local 553, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  9/15/64. Issue: arbitrability - jurisdiction.
- Shell Oil Co. vs. IUOE, Local 525, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  1/22/59. Issue; disciplinary suspension; layoff -arbitrability
- Sheller-Globe Corp. vs. URW, Local 444, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  11/6/72. Issue: discharge - dishonesty - falsification
- Sheller-Globe Corp. vs. AIW, Local 236, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  9/20/71. Issue: discharge - reinstatement after sick leave - inability to perform work
- Sheller Manufacturing Corp. vs. URW, Local 444., 1962 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  3/30/62. Issue: discharge - falsification
- Schultz Folding Box Co. vs. Papercraft Workers' Union No. 409, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  4/22/48. Issue: added duties
- Simmons Co. vs. UIU, Local 422, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  6/3/68. No award. (Case assigned to a different arbitrator.)
- Signal Delivery Service, Inc. vs. Highway and Local Motor Freight Employees, Local 667, 1973 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  5/23/73. Issue: arbitrability - timeliness, suspension, back pay
- Sinclair Refining Co. vs. IUOE, Local 525 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  Issue: layoff - discipline - negligence
- SMW, Local 459, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  7/9/70. Issue: demotion - rates of pay.
- Sioux Falls Argus-Leader vs. Sioux Falls Mailers Union No. 149, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  6/3/70. Issue: rates of pay - wage increases.
- Skelly Oil Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-241, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  11/12/65. Issue: sick leave - sick pay
- Skelly Oil Co., El Dorado Plant vs. OCAW, Local 5-241, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  6/6/66. Issue: claim for pay of a higher classification - failure to assign
- Smith, A. O., Corp. vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, Local 167, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  3/30/61. Issue: promotion.
- Smith, A. O., Corp. vs. BBF, Local 575, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  1/20/66. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Smith and Loveless, Inc. vs. USA, Local 5301, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  7/17/62. Issue: discipline - warnings - layoff.
- Southern Illinois Builders' Association vs. Southern Illinois Laborers' District Council on behalf of Marion, Illinois, Local 577, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  6/22/64. Issue: hiring - hiring halls and union referral
- Southern Illinois Builders' Association vs. Int'l. Hod Carriers', Building and Common Laborers' Union of America, Local 198, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  12/10/64. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Southern Indiana Gas and Electric Co. vs. IBEW, Local 702, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  10/14/55. Issue: crew size.
- Southwestern Bell Telephone Co., Oklahoma City Office vs. Communications Workers of America (CWA), District 6, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 6-7)
  10/29/54. Issue: promotions - seniority
- Southwestern Bell Telephone Co. vs. CWA, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 8-10)
  3/19/73. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Southwestern Electric Co-operative, Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 702, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  5/29/52. Issue: contracts - effective date.
- Southwestern States Telephone Co. vs. CWA, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  2/22/67. Issue: schedules of work - holiday schedules
- Spartan Aircraft Co. vs. IAM, Local 790, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  12/14/59. Issue: supervisors and foremen - return to bargaining unit
- Spartan Printing Co. vs. Int'l. Printing Pressmen's and Assistants' Union of North America, Sparta Printing Pressmen's Union, Local 383, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  10/12/62. Issue: discipline - discharge; reinstatement - following mental illness
- Sperry Rand Corp., Vickers Inc., Joplin Division, Joplin, Maryland vs. AIW, Local 200, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  9/23/57. Issue: discipline - demotion
- Sperry Rand Corp., Vickers Inc., Joplin Division, Joplin, Maryland vs. AIW, Local 200, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  3/16/64. Issue: assignment of jobs - reinstatement
- Sperry Rand Corp., Vickers Division, Jackson, Mississippi vs. IUE, Local 792, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  3/18/69. Issue: rates of pay - claim for pay of higher classification
- Sperry Rand Corp., Vickers Division, Jackson, Mississippi vs. IUE, Local 792, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  12/12/69. No decision
- Sperry Rand Corp., Vickers Division, Jackson, Mississippi vs. IUE, Local 792, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  7/17/73. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Springfield City Lines, Inc. vs. ATU, Division 1249, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  5/5/65. Issue: vacation pay
- Square D Co. vs. IBEW, Local 2220, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  3/12/70. Withdrawn